mobile: +36501360030

Available for relocation: X

location: Budapest, Hungary

GitHub: https://github.com/attila-huszar HackerRank: cinkes CodeWars: cinkes



# **SUMMARY**

With a degree in Socio-Economics, I bring a unique and well-rounded perspective to the technical field. I gained valuable experience in the commercial sector and honed my skills, but I was eager for new experiences, which led me to spend six years abroad as a self-employed individual, teaching me the importance of motivation and self-discipline. Now I'm excited to pursue programming, as I am confident this career path will allow me to apply my problem-solving abilities and keep growing.

# **MOTIVATION**

I am driven by the challenge and satisfaction of programming. I seek out projects that allow me to continuously learn and improve my skills, tackle complex and meaningful tasks, and ultimately make a positive impact. With a strong foundation in problem-solving, I am eager to dive into new and exciting opportunities in the field.

# **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** 

**HUNGARIAN** native

fluent

# Attila Huszár

# JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

# **EDUCATION**

# 2022

# **GREEN FOX ACADEMY,**

JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Workshop phase (10 weeks): TypeScript, Node.js, Express, MySQL, DOM, CSS

Project phase (6 weeks): Adobe Photoshop, Express.js, Git, JWT, MySQL, Node.js, React, SCRUM, NextUI, Sequelize

2003 - 2009

# CORVINUS UNIVERSITY OF BUDAPEST.

SOCIOLOGY AND ECONOMICS (ORGANIZATION SOCIOLOGY),

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# 2017 - 2022

# SELF-EMPLOYED (EDINBURGH, UK),

PRIVATE HIRE CAR DRIVER

- providing a welcoming and positive experience for passengers
- effectively communicating with passengers to understand their needs and address any concerns

# 2015 - 2017

# AMAZON (EDINBURGH, UK),

INVENTORY CONTROL AND QUALITY ASSURANCE

- performing quality checks on incoming and outgoing products
- maintaining accurate and up-to-date records
- collaborating with warehouse team to ensure efficient and effective quality assurance processes

# 2008 - 2015

# DOMI-DÓR KFT (BUDAPEST, HUNGARY),

FINANCE AND PROCUREMENT MANAGER

- managing financial and procurement activities for a small architectural firm
- sourcing and contracting of suppliers
- maintaining IT architecture, enterprise software and produced marketing materials with graphic design tools

